REGINA McSweeney

1201 Carroll Avenue, Duncanville, TX 75137 • Home: 469-759-6674 • Cell: 214-254-0781 • reginal_65@yahoo.com

Professional Summary

pct with 19 years experience in healthcare. Skilled in providing patient care

.

Professionally trained pct with experience ensuring high standards of culturally competent care for a wide variety of patients with . diverse needs.

draw labs and blood sugars daily.

Skills

• Excellent Interpersonal Skills

patient care tec

- Medical Terminology
- Enthusiastic patient care Assistant
- Venipuncture/blood draw expert
- CPR certification
- Foley catheter insertion/removal
- Qualified daily living activity assistant

Work History

pct, 06/1996 to 12/2015

methodist hospital of dallas - 1441 north beckely

- Interviewed patients to obtain medical information, weight and height measurements and vital signs
- Completed clinical rotations in Geriatrics.
- Assessed patients and documented their medical histories.
- Collected blood, for laboratory specimens and prepared them for lab testing.
- Performed vitals/glucose testing

pct, 11/2015 to 02/2016 Baylor of Dallas – dallas tx

care giver, 06/2016 to Current private home care – Dallas

Education

High School Diploma: 95 homeschool - Dallas, TX

Certifications

- CPR certified through American Heart Association
- cna certified